<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ConstraintLayout</string>
    <string name="cambridge_dictionary_dictionary_translate_grammar_log_in_english_uk_follow_us_log_in_english_uk_menu_dictionary_translate_grammar_back_to_home_page_search_term_grammarenglish_frenchfrench_english_meaning_of_scroll_in_the_english_dictionary_english_american_business_scroll_in_english_see_all_translations_scrollnoun_c_uk_skr_l_us_skro_l_a_long_roll_of_paper_or_similar_material_with_usually_official_writing_on_it_the_ancient_egyptians_stored_information_on_scrolls_a_decoration_that_looks_like_a_roll_of_paper_the_tops_of_the_marble_pillars_were_decorated_with_scrolls_thesaurus_synonyms_and_related_words_decorating_or_making_something_attractive_accessorize_adorn_adornment_beautify_bedeck_edged_embellish_festoon_flock_garland_glam_ornament_ornamentation_ornate_pimp_prettify_titivate_twiddly_window_dressing_zhuzh_see_more_results_scrollverb_i_usually_adv_prep_uk_skr_l_us_skro_l_c2_to_move_text_or_other_information_on_a_computer_screen_in_order_to_see_a_different_part_of_it_scroll_to_the_end_of_the_document_thesaurus_synonyms_and_related_words_definition_of_scroll_from_the_cambridge_advanced_learner_s_dictionary_thesaurus_cambridge_university_press_translations_of_scroll_in_french_faire_d_filer_faire_d_filer_vers_le_haut_bas_rouleau_need_a_translator_translator_tool_get_a_quick_free_translation_what_is_the_pronunciation_of_scroll_browse_script_scripted_scripture_scriptwriter_scroll_scroll_bar_scroll_key_scrooge_scrotum_scroll_up_scroll_down_create_and_share_your_own_word_lists_and_quizzes_for_free_sign_up_now_log_in_contents_noun_1_verb_1_more_meanings_of_scroll_scroll_bar_scroll_key_see_all_meanings_word_of_the_day_referendum_a_vote_in_which_all_the_people_in_a_country_or_an_area_are_asked_to_give_their_opinion_about_or_decide_an_important_political_or_social_question_about_this_my_trump_card_words_and_phrases_meaning_advantage_blog_my_trump_card_words_and_phrases_meaning_advantage_september_27_2017_read_more_frequency_patch_noun_new_words_frequency_patch_noun_september_25_2017_more_new_words_search_from_your_browser_add_cambridge_dictionary_to_your_browser_in_a_click_get_our_free_widgets_add_the_power_of_cambridge_dictionary_to_your_website_using_our_free_search_box_widgets_dictionary_apps_browse_our_dictionary_apps_today_and_ensure_you_are_never_again_lost_for_words_learn_new_words_help_in_print_develop_dictionary_api_double_click_lookup_search_widgets_license_data_about_accessibility_cambridge_english_cambridge_university_press_cookies_and_privacy_corpus_terms_of_use_2_30_m_likes_145_k_followers_n_c_fans_cambridge_university_press_2017"><![CDATA[Cambridge Dictionary Dictionary Translate Grammar Log in English (UK) Follow us Log in English (UK) Menu Dictionary Translate Grammar Back to home page Search Term GrammarEnglish–FrenchFrench–English Meaning of “scroll” in the English Dictionary English American Business scroll in English See all translations scrollnoun [ C ] uk ​ /skrəʊl/ us ​ /skroʊl/ ​ a long roll of paper or similar material with usually official writing on it: The ancient Egyptians stored information on scrolls. ​ a decoration that looks like a roll of paper: The tops of the marble pillars were decorated with scrolls. Thesaurus: synonyms and related words Decorating or making something attractive accessorize adorn adornment beautify bedeck edged embellish festoon flock garland glam ornament ornamentation ornate pimp prettify titivate twiddly window dressing zhuzh See more results » scrollverb [ I usually + adv/prep ] uk ​ /skrəʊl/ us ​ /skroʊl/ ​ C2 to move text or other information on a computer screen in order to see a different part of it: Scroll to the end of the document. Thesaurus: synonyms and related words (Definition of “scroll” from the Cambridge Advanced Learner’s Dictionary & Thesaurus © Cambridge University Press) Translations of “scroll” in French faire défiler, faire défiler vers le haut/bas, rouleau… Need a translator? Translator tool Get a quick, free translation! What is the pronunciation of scroll? Browse script scripted scripture scriptwriter scroll scroll bar scroll key scrooge scrotum Scroll up Scroll down Create and share your own word lists and quizzes for free! Sign up now Log in Contents noun (1) verb (1) More meanings of “scroll” scroll bar scroll key See all meanings Word of the Day referendum a vote in which all the people in a country or an area are asked to give their opinion about or decide an important political or social question About this My trump card. (Words and phrases meaning ‘advantage’) Blog My trump card. (Words and phrases meaning ‘advantage’) September 27, 2017 Read More frequency patch noun New Words frequency patch noun September 25, 2017 More new words Search from your browser Add Cambridge Dictionary to your browser in a click! Get our free widgets Add the power of Cambridge Dictionary to your website using our free search box widgets. Dictionary apps Browse our dictionary apps today and ensure you are never again lost for words. Learn New Words Help In Print Develop Dictionary API Double-Click Lookup Search Widgets License Data About Accessibility Cambridge English Cambridge University Press Cookies and Privacy Corpus Terms of Use 2.30 m Likes 145 k Followers N/C Fans © Cambridge University Press 2017]]></string>
</resources>
